let savollar3 = [
    {
      numb: 1,
      question: "alley",
      answer: "D. tor ko'cha",
      options: [
        "A. ko'cha",
        "B. yo'l",
        "C. xiyobon",
        "D. tor ko'cha"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 2,
      question: "ax",
      answer: "B. bolta",
      options: [
        "A. arra",
        "B. bolta",
        "C. bolg'a",
        "D. pichoq"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 3,
      question: "bunch",
      answer: "C. bog'lam",
      options: [
        "A. to'da",
        "B. to'plam",
        "C. bog'lam",
        "D. guruh"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 4,
      question: "chore",
      answer: "A. yumush",
      options: [
        "A. yumush",
        "B. ermak",
        "C. o'yin",
        "D. sevimli ish"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 5,
      question: "decent",
      answer: "D. yaxshigina",
      options: [
        "A. yomon",
        "B. past",
        "C. mukammal",
        "D. yaxshigina"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 6,
      question: "disgrace",
      answer: "B. sharmandalik",
      options: [
        "A. sharaf",
        "B. sharmandalik",
        "C. faxr",
        "D. g'urur"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 7,
      question: "elbow",
      answer: "C. tirsak",
      options: [
        "A. tizza",
        "B. yelka",
        "C. tirsak",
        "D. bilak"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 8,
      question: "grateful",
      answer: "A. minnatdor",
      options: [
        "A. minnatdor",
        "B. beparv–æ",
        "C. norozi",
        "D. noshukur"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 9,
      question: "to irritate",
      answer: "D. g'azablantirmoq",
      options: [
        "A. tinchlantirmoq",
        "B. xursand qilmoq",
        "C. ovutmoq",
        "D. g'azablantirmoq"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 10,
      question: "to kid",
      answer: "B. hazillashmoq",
      options: [
        "A. aldamoq",
        "B. hazillashmoq",
        "C. po'pisa qilmoq",
        "D. ogohlantirmoq"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 11,
      question: "loose",
      answer: "C. bo'sh",
      options: [
        "A. mahkam",
        "B. tor",
        "C. bo'sh",
        "D. tarang"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 12,
      question: "to offend",
      answer: "A. xafa qilmoq",
      options: [
        "A. xafa qilmoq",
        "B. maqtamoq",
        "C. xursand qilmoq",
        "D. ruhlantirmoq"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 13,
      question: "overnight",
      answer: "D. tuni bilan",
      options: [
        "A. kunduzgi",
        "B. ertalabki",
        "C. kechki",
        "D. tuni bilan"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 14,
      question: "to persist",
      answer: "B. qat'iy turmoq",
      options: [
        "A. voz kechmoq",
        "B. qat'iy turmoq",
        "C. shubhalanmoq",
        "D. rad etmoq"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 15,
      question: "pine",
      answer: "C. qarag'ay",
      options: [
        "A. eman",
        "B. qayin",
        "C. qarag'ay",
        "D. terak"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 16,
      question: "scar",
      answer: "A. chandiq",
      options: [
        "A. chandiq",
        "B. yara",
        "C. tirnalgan joy",
        "D. kesik"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 17,
      question: "sensation",
      answer: "D. his-tuyg'u",
      options: [
        "A. fikr",
        "B. g'oya",
        "C. xotira",
        "D. his-tuyg'u"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 18,
      question: "sled",
      answer: "B. chana",
      options: [
        "A. velosiped",
        "B. chana",
        "C. samokat",
        "D. skeytbord"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 19,
      question: "to tease",
      answer: "C. masxara qilmoq",
      options: [
        "A. maqtamoq",
        "B. qo'llab-quvvatlamoq",
        "C. masxara qilmoq",
        "D. ruhlantirmoq"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 20,
      question: "valentine",
      answer: "A. mashuqa",
      options: [
        "A. mashuqa",
        "B. do'st",
        "C. tanish",
        "D. hamkasb"
      ]
    }
  ];
  
  export default savollar3;